[
  {
    "question": "If Michael Cimino hadn't impressed Clint Eastwood, who would have directed \"Thunderbolt and Lightfoot\"?",
    "answer": "Clint Eastwood"
  },
  {
    "question": "If John Hughes' short story \"Vacation '58\" was titled to reflect a year later, what would the year in the title be?",
    "answer": "1959"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Caroline Flack's mother had felt the name suited her, what would have been Caroline's name?",
    "answer": "Caroline"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Voorhees hadn't decided to incorporate the Friday the 13th references into their name, how many tracks would each side of \"Spilling Blood Without Reason\" have contained?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "If there hadn't been a shortage of ships and sailors, whose expansion into the Northwest coast beyond Prince William Sound would not have been delayed?",
    "answer": "Russian entry or Russian expansion"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Richard II hadn't reduced Bolingbroke's sentence in the Shakespeare play \"Richard II\", how many years would Bolingbroke have been banished for?",
    "answer": "10 or ten"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Grand Crown Marshal Stanisław Herakliusz Lubomirski had utilized the garden pavilions in the Ujazdów Castle for their original intent, what kind of facility would have been initially established?",
    "answer": "ornate bath chamber"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Nick Mangold from the New York Jets and Maurkice Pouncey from the Pittsburgh Steelers had been able to participate in the 2011 Pro Bowl, who wouldn't have been chosen as the alternate center?",
    "answer": "Alex Mack or C Alex Mack"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the slurry pipeline that fed slurried coal from the rail cars into the gasifier hadn't experienced corrosion, which project wouldn't have been initially shut down?",
    "answer": "Polk County IGCC or Wabash River"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Paramore hadn't decided to finish their 2009 album in Calabasas, California, where would they have likely recorded it instead?",
    "answer": "Nashville"
  },
  {
    "question": "If \"The Great Dinosaur Discovery\" documentary was indeed produced, when was it first premiered?",
    "answer": "November 13, 1973"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Kanye West had not decided to invite Lil Wayne to feature on the track \"Barry Bonds\", what would \"Graduation\" have been devoid of?",
    "answer": "Guest rap verses"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the song \"Overjoyed\" had been included in the album \"Journey Through 'The Secret Life of Plants'\", on which subsequent album would it not have been featured?",
    "answer": "\"In Square Circle\""
  },
  {
    "question": "If India had lost in the 2007 ICC World Twenty20 finals, which team would have won the match?",
    "answer": "Pakistan"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Pluto were not a part of the Solar System, which would be the most massive and largest known dwarf planet?",
    "answer": "Eris"
  },
  {
    "question": "If there hadn't been a scarcity of directors post the Cultural Revolution when Zhang Yimou completed his film school, what would his initial role have been?",
    "answer": "assistant or Director's assistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Henry Hoare I, the 17th-century English banker and landowner, had fathered two additional children with his wife Jane Benson, what would their total number of children be?",
    "answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "question": "If NBN Television's inauguration had been delayed by a month, in which month would it have been launched?",
    "answer": "April"
  },
  {
    "question": "If an additional disc was included in the \"F-Zero GX/AX Original Soundtracks\" release, what would be the total number of discs in the set?",
    "answer": "3 or three"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the ceasefire and the 'dump arms' order hadn't been issued on 24 May 1923, which conflict would have continued?",
    "answer": "Irish Civil war"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the creators of \"The Idolmaster\" video game had not decided to reduce the number of idols, how many idols would have originally been included in the game?",
    "answer": "12 or 13"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the lead single \"Eat, Sleep, Wake (Nothing but You)\" by Bombay Bicycle Club had been released exactly one week prior, what would have been its release date?",
    "answer": "August 20, 2019"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the original prototype of \"And Yet It Moves\" at the Vienna University of Technology hadn't won or been nominated for awards, which game might not have been fully developed and released?",
    "answer": "And Yet it Moves"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the \"SaGa Frontier Original Sound Track\" album had been released with 15 fewer tracks, how many tracks would it have contained?",
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Kerry Katona had not become pregnant, who would not have replaced her in the musical group?",
    "answer": "Jenny Frost"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the 1939 proposals for the Metropolitan line in England hadn't been abandoned due to World War II, which station would have stayed open during peak hours for interchange with the Bakerloo line?",
    "answer": "Swiss Cottage or Swiss Cottage station"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the evening newscasts in Singapore had not been extended to 90 minutes, at what time would prime time have originally started?",
    "answer": "19:00"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Rajasthan Royals had lost in the 2008 Indian Premier League finals, who would have been declared the winner?",
    "answer": "Chennai Super Kings"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Milton Dinhofer had manufactured his straws in the original scissor shape, what would they not have featured?",
    "answer": "character or characters"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the \"Regio corpo truppe coloniali della Somalia Italiana\" had retained its original name, what would it have been referred to as in English in 1910?",
    "answer": "Guard Corps of Benadir"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the original melody for Princeton's \"Old Nassau\" had been maintained, which tune would it have been sung to?",
    "answer": "Auld Lang Syne"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the significance of weight-saving had not been recognized, what would not have happened to the vertebrae of sauropods like \"Camarasaurus\"?",
    "answer": "hollowed out or hollow out"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the manufacturing process hadn't encountered ink problems, what color would The Hulk originally have been?",
    "answer": "grey"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Stanford University hadn't had computer systems on campus in the early 1980s, which company's initial product wouldn't have been rooted in Stanford's technology?",
    "answer": "Cisco"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Senator Tammy Duckworth had introduced the bill S.2086 concurrently with the original introduction of HR 3677 in the House of Representatives, in what year would she have presented it to the Senate?",
    "answer": "2017"
  },
  {
    "question": "If another state had ratified the United States Constitution prior to New Jersey, what would have been New Jersey's ratification position?",
    "answer": "fourth"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the extension of the Seibu Shinjuku Line from Takadanobaba Station to Seibu Shinjuku Station had been postponed by a year, in what year would the expansion have been completed?",
    "answer": "1953"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the city in Texas, currently named after Houston lumberman Isaac Conroe, had been named after a different individual, what name would it not carry?",
    "answer": "Conroe"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Kaori Yuki hadn't been concerned about concluding the story appropriately, how many chapters would \"Angel Sanctuary\" have originally contained?",
    "answer": "Ten"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the group initially known as the \"Corinthian 15\" hadn't expanded, how many members would it have had?",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Octagon in Egypt hadn't been constructed, which building would have remained the largest defense headquarters and office building complex in the world?",
    "answer": "The Pentagon"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Bharti Airtel Limited from India had not purchased a majority stake in Warid Telecom, which entity would have retained majority ownership?",
    "answer": "Warid Telecom or Warid Telecom International LLC"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the series \"Metalocalypse\" hadn't encountered trademark issues, what would its original name have been?",
    "answer": "Deathclock"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Earl Sweatshirt had continued to use his birth name in his music career, what name would his fans recognize him by?",
    "answer": "Thebe Neruda Kgositsile"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Albi Cathedral in the Tarn Department, France, had maintained its original purpose, what would it have been used as?",
    "answer": "Fortress"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the film \"Kiki's Delivery Service\" had not been expanded, what would have been its original runtime?",
    "answer": "60 minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Norman Foster hadn't received any architectural commissions in 1981, which city's airport terminal would he not have been involved in designing?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Hicham El Guerrouj had run a second slower on 7 July 1999 in Roma, who would have held the world record for the fastest mile run?",
    "answer": "Noah Ngeny"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Michigan Department of Natural Resources had granted the filming permit for the \"Amazing Race\" episode featuring a performance by The White Stripes, where would the episode have been filmed?",
    "answer": "Belle Isle Park (Michigan) or Belle Isle Park or Belle Isle Park, Michigan"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the album \"Live and Let Die\" had been released as originally planned, in which year would it have been launched?",
    "answer": "1991"
  },
  {
    "question": "If M-PESA had not been expanded to serve as a general money-transfer system, what would its primary function have been?",
    "answer": "microfinance-loan repayments"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Peter Canavan hadn't been worried about Tyrone potentially losing by one of the largest margins in Ulster Championship history due to the Down attack, what action would he not have taken?",
    "answer": "Stepped up or Down attack"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Duryodhana had not been made the new crown prince of Hastinapura, who would have retained the position?",
    "answer": "Yudhishthira"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Mýa had chosen to honor Janet Jackson at the MTV Icon event, which song would she have performed?",
    "answer": "The Pleasure Principle"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Mylène Farmer's album \"Interstellaires\" had been released a week ahead of its original schedule, what would have been its release date?",
    "answer": "October 30, 2015"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the 1944 procurement order for 9 mm conversion kits for the M3 submachine guns had not been changed and remained at the original quantity requested, how many kits would Rock Island Arsenal and Buffalo Arms Corporation have been asked to manufacture?",
    "answer": "25,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the communist high command hadn't radioed the East China Field Army, where would the communist 2nd and 7th Columns have been deployed?",
    "answer": "Central China"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the region where Central Cortada is currently situated had retained its original name, what would it be referred to as during the 1700s?",
    "answer": "Estancia Descalabrado"
  },
  {
    "question": "If software technology had been advanced earlier, how many years prior would Williams have designed the \"Phantasmagoria\" video game?",
    "answer": "Eight years"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Peck School had retained its original name since its establishment in 1893, what would it be known as today?",
    "answer": "Miss Sutphen's School"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Montreal Canadiens hadn't won the 1993 Stanley Cup Finals, which team would have been the champions?",
    "answer": "Los Angeles Kings"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the character \"The Blob\" from Marvel Comics didn't possess an extreme amount of pliable body mass, which superhuman ability would he be without?",
    "answer": "superhuman strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were tuning in for the premiere of the TV series animated by Bibury Animation Studios, which is based on the video game Azur Lane, on what date would you have been watching it?",
    "answer": "October 3, 2019"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Lyons Avenue in the Fifth Ward of Houston, Texas had not been renamed, what would its original name be?",
    "answer": "Odin Avenue"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the second-place team in the total medal count at the 1992 Summer Olympics in Barcelona, Spain, had won an additional 10 medals, which country would have topped the medal tally?",
    "answer": "United States"
  },
  {
    "question": "If an employee of The Weinstein Company transitioned to Lantern Entertainment immediately after The Weinstein Company ceased operations, when could they have started their new role?",
    "answer": "July 16, 2018"
  },
  {
    "question": "If \"Killer Within\" is a post-apocalyptic horror television series, how many million viewers did it attract upon its initial broadcast in the United States?",
    "answer": "9.27 million"
  },
  {
    "question": "If trucks had never been invented, what methods would have been used to transport oil from Pennsylvania?",
    "answer": "barges or boats"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the PC game Dune II was only compatible with the platform it was initially released on, what platform would you need to play it?",
    "answer": "DOS"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Hezbollah had never been established, whose followers would not have been instrumental in its formation during the early 1980s?",
    "answer": "Ruhollah Khomeini or Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini or Ayatollah Khomeini"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Becky Lynch hadn't been injured before Survivor Series, who would have been Ronda Rousey's opponent in the non-title match?",
    "answer": "Becky Lynch"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Toronto streetcar system had not been established, which religious group would have faced difficulty in attending Sunday services?",
    "answer": "Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the role of Lea de Castro in the 2006 Austrian art-house film Klimt had not been recast, which actress was originally supposed to portray her?",
    "answer": "Laetitia Casta"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Channel 39, originally owned by the WKY Television System, was sold in 1976, who became its new owner?",
    "answer": "Gaylord Broadcasting"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Italy had not emerged victorious in the final match of the 1934 FIFA World Cup, which team would have been crowned the champions?",
    "answer": "Czechoslovakia"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Jeff Gordon hadn't faced licensing issues associated with Days of Thunder in 1993, which car number would he have driven instead of No. 24?",
    "answer": "No. 46"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the establishment of the Kentucky Educational Television program had been postponed by a year, in which year would it have been initiated?",
    "answer": "1990"
  },
  {
    "question": "If David Ramsey hadn't reprised his role as John Diggle in the \"Supergirl\" series, in how many other Arrowverse series would he have appeared?",
    "answer": "4 or four"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Ministry of Defence (MINDEF) of Singapore had not approached Jack Neo, which military-themed film would he not have been able to create?",
    "answer": "Ah Boys to Men"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the \"BraviSEAmo!\" show had not been replaced in the Mediterranean Harbor in 2011, which show would not have premiered at Tokyo DisneySea that year?",
    "answer": "Fantasmic!"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Gustavo Saba had not won the 2016 Codasur South American Rally Championship, who would have been the champion?",
    "answer": "Diego Domínguez"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Richter's aunt had not developed schizophrenia, who would not have murdered her as depicted in \"Never Look Away\"?",
    "answer": "Nazis"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the city of Vienna in Austria was exclusively referred to by its Slovene name, what would it be known as?",
    "answer": "Dunaj"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Breitkopf & Härtel hadn't been the original publishers of Liszt's Symphonic Poems, when would they have been legally allowed to publish the work without needing permission?",
    "answer": "1916"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Joe Biden had lost the 2020 US presidential elections, who would have been the president?",
    "answer": "Donald Trump"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Qur'anic verses had not established that polytheism is incompatible with the creation of the universe, which characteristic of God would be disputed?",
    "answer": "oneness"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the 1989 Holly Farms 400 race hadn't been postponed due to rain, on what date would it have taken place?",
    "answer": "October 1, 1989"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez hadn't proposed any concept during his first presidential campaign in 1998, which concept wouldn't have been introduced in Argentina?",
    "answer": "Bank of the South"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Matthew Bannister's takeover of BBC Radio 1 had been postponed by a year, in which year would he have fully assumed control?",
    "answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the \"Three Men and a Comic Book\" episode of \"The Simpsons\" had premiered one month after its original air date, in which month would it have been broadcasted?",
    "answer": "June"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Kanye West and Kid Cudi hadn't reunited in 2016 for the production of the album \"Kids See Ghosts\", when was the last time they collaborated?",
    "answer": "2008"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the city in Klamath County, Oregon had retained its original name, what would it be known as today?",
    "answer": "Linkville"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Isleños peoples had not established a settlement in the San Bernardo community, how many original communities would they have settled in Louisiana?",
    "answer": "3 or three"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Fullerton Hotel Singapore had been commissioned in 1914 instead of 1924, how many years later would it have been from the end of Robert Fullerton's term as the first Governor of the Straits Settlements?",
    "answer": "85 years later"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the original plan for California State Route 54, stretching from eastern National City and Valley Road to La Presa and Jamacha Road, had been implemented, how many lanes would the road have had?",
    "answer": "8 or eight"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the initial vessels of the \"Leninsky Komsomol\"-class cargo ship line were designed with double the number of berths, how many people could they have accommodated?",
    "answer": "102"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Rachel Shenton's final scenes as Mitzeee Minniver in the show had been broadcasted a day later than the original schedule, on what date would they have been aired?",
    "answer": "February 16, 2013"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Tatiana Maslany had not been chosen for the lead role, who was the other actor considered for the part?",
    "answer": "Elliot Page"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the pKa values of acids and bases in solutions aren't known, what aspect of their behavior can't be understood quantitatively?",
    "answer": "quantitative or Quantitative behaviour"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Lynas Advance Materials Plant in Western Australia had started its operations a year later than originally planned, in which year would it have commenced?",
    "answer": "2013"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Jean Genet had published his semiautobiographical work \"Our Lady of the Flowers\" two years prior, in which year would it have been released?",
    "answer": "1941"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Frank Waters hadn't been working on \"Tombstone Travesty\", which city would he not have needed to research in?",
    "answer": "Tombstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Civil Rights March had taken place on US 80, who would have led the Selma to Montgomery marches?",
    "answer": "Martin Luther King Jr"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Mamas and the Papas had not disbanded, who would not have pursued a solo singing career?",
    "answer": "Cass Elliot"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Catholic University of America hadn't been established in Washington D.C., where would the Eastern Province Dominicans have relocated the Pontifical Faculty of the Immaculate Conception?",
    "answer": "Somerset, Ohio"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the XFL had continued to be owned by its original proprietor, who would that individual be?",
    "answer": "Vince McMahon"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the train route from San Joaquin Valley via the Tehachapi Loop had not included any bridges, how would the transportation of \"El Gobernador\" have been affected?",
    "answer": "not disassembled"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Dalesman magazine had not expanded its coverage, which region would it primarily serve?",
    "answer": "Yorkshire Dales"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the American monster film \"Monster Hunter\" hadn't experienced any postponements due to the COVID-19 pandemic, when was its original release date scheduled?",
    "answer": "September 4, 2020"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the AI research funded by SCI in 1983 had been underway at 108 institutions by 1985, how many more institutions would that be compared to the actual number?",
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Mike Bliss had returned to full-time status two years prior to 2011, in which decade would this have occurred?",
    "answer": "2000s"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the film \"Bullet Train\" hadn't faced any postponements, when was it originally scheduled to be released?",
    "answer": "April 8, 2022"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Royal Palace of Alexandru Ioan Cuza in Ruginoasa, Romania, had remained in the possession of its original owners, which family would it belong to?",
    "answer": "Sturza"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Chennai Super Kings had been defeated in the 2010 Indian Premier League Final, which team would have emerged as the winner?",
    "answer": "Mumbai Indians"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Netherlands hadn't lost the colony in the Cape of Good Hope, where would the duit coins, dated 1802-1809, not have been sent?",
    "answer": "East Indies or Indies"
  },
  {
    "question": "If JT the Bigga Figga hadn't owned Get Low Recordz, which record label would The Game not have been able to sign a deal with in 2002?",
    "answer": "Get Low Recordz"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the bloodless coup in 1968 had not taken place in Iraq, who would have continued to serve as the president?",
    "answer": "Abdul Rahman Arif"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Manchester City hadn't secured victory in the 2011-2012 Premier League season, which team would have claimed the title?",
    "answer": "Manchester United F.C. or Manchester United or Man Utd"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the first rape kit developed in Chicago in the mid-1970s was named after the person who initially researched and proposed it to R. Vitullo, what would its name have been?",
    "answer": "Goddard kit"
  },
  {
    "question": "If one less tankōbon volume of the \"Hunter × Hunter\" manga had been released by October 4, 2018, what would have been the total count?",
    "answer": "35 or thirty-five"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Vassilus Spanoulis' agent hadn't arranged his contract, after how many years would he not have been able to opt out?",
    "answer": "One year"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the COVID-19 pandemic hadn't caused delays, when would the American movie \"Nine Days\" have been originally released in theaters?",
    "answer": "January 22, 2021"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the medium-density unit building, Minimbah Court, in Yarralumla, Australia had been constructed a decade earlier, in which decade would it have been built?",
    "answer": "1940s"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the number of steps on the steep stairway at the Preah Vihear Temple's modern entrance were doubled, how many steps would there be?",
    "answer": "326"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Mimic's heroic counterpart from the parallel world Earth-12 didn't have a power restriction, how many mutant powers could he potentially copy?",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Federal and Territorial Building in Alaska had maintained its original purpose after its construction, what entity would be using the building?",
    "answer": "federal government"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the members of Quest Crew hadn't disbanded, which dance troupe would they have continued to perform with?",
    "answer": "SickStep"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Gloster Meteor F.8 had not been redesigned, how many cannons would it have been equipped with?",
    "answer": "6 or six"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Barack Obama had lost the 2008 US presidential election, who would have been elected as the president?",
    "answer": "John McCain"
  },
  {
    "question": "If James Madison had not been concerned about the potential for corruption through the creation of unnecessary public offices and salary increases for personal gain, at which event would he not have voiced this fear?",
    "answer": "Philadelphia Convention in 1787"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the city of Streator, Illinois, continued to primarily produce what it initially started with, what would be its main product?",
    "answer": "coal"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Mindless Self Indulgence, a band that started in 1995, decided to take a break, when did they announce their hiatus?",
    "answer": "2014 or January 2014"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Pat Quinn hadn't learned that the Edmonton Oilers intended to draft Bure, in which round would he not have selected him in the ice hockey draft?",
    "answer": "Sixth"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Justin Trudeau had not emerged victorious in the October 14, 2008 election in Papineau, who would have likely been the winner?",
    "answer": "Vivian Barbot"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Jean-Baptiste Gustave Le Gray had been born one day earlier, what would have been his birth date?",
    "answer": "August 29, 1820"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Bersih 2.0 rally had been moved to Merdeka Stadium, where was it initially planned to be held?",
    "answer": "Streets of Kuala Lumpur"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the school in the St Paul's Cray area of the London Borough of Bromley, England had never undergone a name change, what would its original names have remained?",
    "answer": "Midfield secondary for Girls or Midfield secondary for Boys"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Panzer III had been introduced one year later into World War II, what would have been its inaugural year of use?",
    "answer": "1940"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the \"oversight\" features to the MediaWiki software had not been added, who would not have been able to monitor the tool's use?",
    "answer": "Oversighters"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Burt Reynolds hadn't pulled out of the film Zardoz, who would have been his co-star alongside Charlotte Rampling?",
    "answer": "Burt Reynolds"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the great Sicilian earthquake of 1693 had not occurred, how many towns and cities would have been preserved in Sicily by 1694?",
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the director had followed his original plan for the movie \"Sweet and Lowdown\", who would have portrayed the character Emmet Ray?",
    "answer": "Woody Allen"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the duo hadn't rebranded themselves as Salt-N-Pepa, what would their original name have been?",
    "answer": "Super Nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Aishwarya Rai Bachchan and Pakistani actress Nadia Jamil had not turned down the role of Saamiya Siddiqui in the film Veer-Zaara, which actress would have missed the opportunity?",
    "answer": "Rani Mukerji"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the character Dean Winchester from the WB show \"Supernatural\" was named after the actor originally intended, who would that actor be?",
    "answer": "Harrison Ford"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Boris Nemtsov had not been assassinated, in which legislature would the re-election not have taken place?",
    "answer": "Yaroslavl regional parliament"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Jean Marc Mormeck, the French heavyweight, hadn't been lined up to challenge the then-unified world champion Wladimir Klitschko, who would he not have declined the opportunity to fight?",
    "answer": "Alexander Povetkin"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Andrew Jackson had been defeated in the 1832 United States presidential election, who would have been the president from the National Republican Party?",
    "answer": "Henry Clay"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the coronavirus pandemic hadn't delayed the construction of the new terminal at the Pittsburgh International Airport, when was it originally scheduled to open?",
    "answer": "2023"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the town of Telluride in Colorado had retained its original name, what would we be calling it today?",
    "answer": "Columbia"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Confederate States of America had lost the battle, which entity would have emerged victorious?",
    "answer": "United States"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the land parcel of the Hoornbeek Store Complex in Napanoch, New York, United States were tripled in size, how many acres would it encompass?",
    "answer": "3 or three"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the 89th Infantry Regiment of the 4th Army (Kingdom of Yugoslavia) had proceeded to its original destination, which division would they have joined?",
    "answer": "17th ID or 17th Infantry Division \"Vrbaska\" (17th ID)"
  },
  {
    "question": "If laminations were not incorporated in the stator of an electric motor, what type of energy losses would not be minimized?",
    "answer": "induced circulating eddy current or Induction circulating eddy current"
  },
  {
    "question": "If children did not start learning a second language at the age of 7 or younger, what aspect of this second language would they be slower to achieve?",
    "answer": "fluency or Full fluency"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Spanish Armada, which sailed against England in 1588, had not experienced a change in leadership, who would have been its sole commander?",
    "answer": "Alvaro de Bazan"
  },
  {
    "question": "If \"This American Life\" had strictly adhered to the original concept of Public Radio International, which medium would it not have utilized for distribution?",
    "answer": "digital cinema"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Hidenori Shoji hadn't contributed to the musical score of the video game \"F-Zero GX\", who would have been the only composer?",
    "answer": "Daiki Kasho"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the 2020 superhero film \"The New Mutants\" had been released on its original date, which major superhero film would it have competed with in theaters?",
    "answer": "Deadpool 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Sir Rowland St John KB had become a member of the House of Commons five years prior to his actual joining, in which century would that have been?",
    "answer": "1600s or 17th"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Mongolian horse has connections with other breeds, where were these horses originally imported from?",
    "answer": "Russia"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Barksdale Air Force Base had been constructed at the location initially proposed by Shreveport, which water body would it have been near?",
    "answer": "Cross Lake"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Great Britain, as the primary sponsor of the Treaty of Paris, had agreed to the death penalty for privateers, what would have been a potential consequence?",
    "answer": "prosecution in American courts"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Covid-19 pandemic had been effectively controlled in its early stages, in which year would the ICC Men's T20 World Cup 2020 have taken place?",
    "answer": "2020"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Kelsey Grammer's lines hadn't been cut from \"The Simpsons Movie,\" which character would have had additional dialogue?",
    "answer": "Sideshow Bob"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the colloquial name \"Irish League\" was not used, what would be the formal name of the football league in Northern Ireland?",
    "answer": "Northern Ireland Football League or NIFL"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Barbados Tridents had lost in the 2019 Caribbean Premier League, who would have been the champions?",
    "answer": "Guyana Amazon Warriors"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the size of the alloy wheels on the British Vauxhall VXR were doubled, what would their diameter be?",
    "answer": "40\""
  },
  {
    "question": "If Moses Annenberg hadn't encountered Capone, who would likely not have been invited to the Atlantic City Conference?",
    "answer": "Moses Annenberg"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Manchu queue hairstyle was originally adopted by twice the number of groups mentioned, how many groups would have initially used the style?",
    "answer": "2 or two"
  },
  {
    "question": "If George W. Bush had lost the 2000 United States presidential election, who would have become the president?",
    "answer": "Al Gore"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Aerated Bread Company Ltd had not initially started as a bakery and was instead established in the year they began operating tea rooms, when would the company have been founded?",
    "answer": "1864"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the STS-121 mission hadn't been postponed by NASA, in what year would it have originally launched?",
    "answer": "2005"
  },
  {
    "question": "If segregation hadn't been enforced at NASA Langley Research Center in 1961, who would have been allowed to use the same dining and bathroom facilities?",
    "answer": "Black women or All female mathematicians or All employees"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Minnie Lucie Channing's son, born in 1916, had retained his birth name, what would it be?",
    "answer": "Peter"
  },
  {
    "question": "If FC Nyva Vinnytsia, the Ukrainian football club, hadn't been reformed after it initially folded, in what year would it have ceased operations?",
    "answer": "2005"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Progressive Party of Saskatchewan had not existed, which groups' economic policies would have remained unchallenged in Central Canada?",
    "answer": "Financial and industrial interests or Financial and industrial interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Oliver St John had never been born, how many brothers would Sir Rowland St John KB have had?",
    "answer": "4 or four"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Terminal 2 had not been constructed at Dublin Airport, which pier would have avoided demolition?",
    "answer": "Pier C"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a player in Australian rules football is unable to kick the ball, what is the secondary method they could use?",
    "answer": "Handball"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Turkish Cypriot and Druze Arab lineages have been present for 10 thousand years, what percentage of them carry the V13 SNP mutation?",
    "answer": "More than 10%"
  },
  {
    "question": "If cap gun toys continued to be made from their original material, what would that material be?",
    "answer": "cast iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the original third draft script from April 1980 had been used for the film \"Happy Birthday to Me\", who would have been portrayed as the killer?",
    "answer": "Virginia"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Kenneth Stanley \"Bud\" Adams, Jr. had not ventured into the football business, which National Football League franchise would not have been established?",
    "answer": "Tennessee Titans"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Beneden Merwede stretch of river in the Netherlands were to double in length, how many kilometers long would it be?",
    "answer": "29.6"
  },
  {
    "question": "If another lake surpassed Lake Mead in volume when full, what would be Lake Mead's rank as the largest reservoir in the United States?",
    "answer": "2nd"
  },
  {
    "question": "If St Vincent's Hospital in Sydney, Australia had maintained its original university affiliation, which university would it be associated with?",
    "answer": "University of Sydney"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Republican nominee had emerged victorious in the 2021 New York City mayoral election, who would have assumed the role of mayor?",
    "answer": "Curtis Sliwa"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Tony Mrakovich had not faced difficulties during the Bristol race practice, who would not have been chosen to replace him?",
    "answer": "Dylan Lupton"
  },
  {
    "question": "If cyclones were still utilized in their original function, what kind of gases would they be responsible for cleaning up?",
    "answer": "dust-laden or dust-laden gases"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the ship \"Itasca\" needed to communicate with the plane, what frequency of kHz signal should it transmit?",
    "answer": "500 kHz signal."
  },
  {
    "question": "If the groundbreaking ceremony for the Kingdome had been delayed by one year after the King Street site received approval from the county council, in which year would it have occurred?",
    "answer": "1973"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the political association now known as the Commonwealth of Nations had never altered its original name, what would it be referred to as today?",
    "answer": "British Commonwealth of Nations"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Ligado Networks had been established a year prior, in what year would it have been founded?",
    "answer": "2014"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the Toronto Maple Leafs had not emerged victorious in the 1962 Stanley Cup Finals, which team would have been declared the champions?",
    "answer": "Chicago Blackhawks or Chicago Black Hawks"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Hadise Açıkgöz, the Belgian-Turkish performer, didn't have a younger brother named Murat, how many siblings would she have had during her childhood?",
    "answer": "2 or two"
  },
  {
    "question": "If McCulloch hadn't proposed \"The Venture Bros.\" as an animated series, what would it have originally been?",
    "answer": "comic book story"
  },
  {
    "question": "If WOR radio had not moved its license from its original market, where would it still be licensed?",
    "answer": "Newark"
  },
  {
    "question": "If Mark Millar had declined the offer to write \"Ultimate X-Men\", who was the original choice to pen the comic?",
    "answer": "Brian Michael Bendis"
  },
  {
    "question": "If there had been no frequent arguments on the set during the filming of Days of Thunder, how much delay could have been avoided?",
    "answer": "3 months"
  }
]